Music I just finished editing tomorrow's video, and it's really early on a Thursday for that, so I'm excited.
I actually was supposed to have school today, but I had been emailing with a school counselor asking to switch
My schedule so I could have classes on Wednesday instead.
So I fully thought I was going to school today until I got a change last second.
It's 12.30 now.
I'm gonna head to a little grocery store or stand, like a farmer's produce stand, whatever, and get some groceries
For lunch, and then finish up my video.
I just have some finishing touches, and that's kind of it.
People are looking at me.
And then that should be that.
Okay you guys, I'm back home.
Went and picked up some needed groceries slash produce.
I'm gonna make some lunch now because I'm starving.
Then I'm getting dinner with my friend Eliza who has been in my vlogs before.
She's visited New York a few times and she's actually living abroad in London right now for a little bit.
So she like popped on over to Paris and is leaving tomorrow.
I was sick up until like yesterday and Loki's still recovering today.
So we weren't able to hang out until now.
But at least I get to see each other.
Bye!
Let's make tuna salad because that's all I'd be making for lunch here.
Lunchtime.
Look how good the produce looks.
So fresh and delicious.
It's every time.
So yummy.
We have a little visitor.
We're eating lunch together.
I'm going
To
The next one.
You guys I literally ventured out well first of all I had to go get a tax form for a
Purchase that I made but then I was like I really want to get a journal so I started looking
For a stationery store I found that cute stationery store didn't buy anything wasn't exactly what I was looking for
Pop into a random vintage store across the street and they had exactly what I was looking for like as
I walk in I'm like let me just go in and see what they have they had a little set
Of these traveler notebooks like similar to the Luis Carmen and there's another brand like these they're very popular whatever
Where you can like store multiple journals inside and it's so beautiful and it comes with a little heart charm
Like I'm just in awe and in shock that I found what I was looking for within five minutes of
Me thinking about it crazy Crazy, crazy.
Anyways, I'm going home now before dinner.
Getting ready for dinner with Eliza.
My roommate and I went to this restaurant together and it was really, really good.
Such a cute interior.
It's a Mexican restaurant and I believe they have different locations.
Such a good vibe, really good food.
So that's where I'm taking Eliza tonight.
She's leaving tomorrow at like 7 a.m.
I'm sad I wasn't able to like see her before tonight, like right before she leaves, but I was sick
And just not feeling well.
If you guys saw my last vlog, you would know.
I am feeling a lot better, which is really, really good.
Also my current favorite lip combination is the MAC Lip Liner in Cork.
And then, I mean, I look crazy right now, but you'll see in a second.
The YSL Candy Glaze Stick, neutral shade, O2.
It's really cute, I love it.
It's like a nice little dark nude color combo.
Okay, so you look a little crazy and then you take this and you smudge it out
Dun-dun-dun-dun-dun It's just like a nice subtle brown and this is such it's almost like a lip balm It literally
Is a lip balm Especially if you get the shade because it doesn't really have much of a color and
It is so moisturizing but still a little bit Glossy love it.
I actually purchased this a few days ago because the first time I tried it YSL sent it to me
Thank you YSL and I fell in love with it So I was like I need to buy it again
And then these lip liners are just so good and creamy and like you get a bang for your buck
Cuz look how long it Is like it's a good lip liner.
Anyways, that's all on my jeans.
I'm literally we're watching.
I didn't really change I changed into sweatpants when I got home, but I'm gonna wear the same outfit I
Was wearing all day today.
We're on a YSL kick not sponsored But I want to wear this perfume and I'm ready to go and
I'm ready to go Alright you at dinner
Hi!
It's Eliza in Paris!
And look at her cute bob!
Last time we saw her, she had hair up to like here.
Yeah, I chalked it all off.
Girl, it's so chic.
It's so cute.
It's giving Paris.
It's so giving Paris.
You should move here.
Like hello.
Why literally wood in Armenia?
I love it.
Girl, it's so chic.
It's so cute.
It's giving parents.
It's so giving parents.
You should move here.
Like, hello.
Why literally wouldn't I be?
Hi, and welcome to this short guided meditation designed to help bring a moment of calm and clarity into your
Day.
Take three big deep breaths, breathing in through the nose and out through
The mouth.
Good morning, you guys.
I just finished my five minute meditation.
I've been really trying to meditate a lot more often because with my change to a whole new
City, let alone a whole new country, obviously emotions come with that.
And it's been mostly exciting emotions, but there are times that I find myself, especially in the morning where my
Anxiety tends to be a lot higher, I have had to find ways to kind of come back to
Myself, come back to my body, and really focus on the present moment and not be so quick to rush
Into my day.
I have such a big problem with rushing through my day, thinking of all the million things I need to
Do and how I need to get them all done, thinking about what I'm doing tomorrow or next
Week, and I just tend to lose myself along the way and forget that the present moment is the most
Important.
So I really find that setting up a good practice at at the beginning of your day, when you're freshly
Awoken, if you will, is the best way to kind of kickstart your day in a positive way.
And it also has helped me just really ground myself throughout the rest of the day.
If I find myself in a super stressful moment or my anxiety tends to be higher, even the five minutes
That I took that morning to meditate and ground myself and breathe, it makes such a big difference.
And I notice a difference when I don't do it.
I really make sure that I'm making space for mindfulness, especially in the morning.
But if not, I also love to do it at the end of the day when I want to unwind
And just calm my brain down before I go to bed.
I honestly used to be so intimidated by meditating because I thought I had to be this grand practice that
Took up a large chunk of your morning, but it really doesn't have to be.
And I actually find that five to 10 minutes works best for me.
I've been especially loving the jumpstart your day meditation on Headspace.
It's super simple and it only takes five minutes, like I just said, and it's mostly focused on the breath
And coming back to the breath, coming back to the body.
And I find such a big difference by the end of those short five minutes.
I feel so much more calm and regulated, ready to start my day.
And actually it's been proven that just five minutes a day of headspace reduces stress.
And after 10 days of headspace, your happiness is proven to increase, which is amazing.
And because it is still fairly early in the new year, it is the perfect time to set another goal
And start meditating if you're interested.
So I will leave the link in the description box below, or you can scan the QR code and get
60 days of headspace for free.
It's two months of full free access compared to the standard two week trial that they have on their website.
So I highly recommend you guys check it out and a big thank you to Headspace for sponsoring today's video.
Guys, I'm so obsessed with my journal.
So cute.
I think after I get ready for the day, I'm gonna honestly go out for a little
Adventure, find a cute little coffee shop and sit and write in my journal.
I don't know about what, but I'm sure I'll come up with something.
I'm about to open this PR package.
Jaded London.
Thank you guys.
I'm so excited.
Like when they reached out, I was like, hello.
Hi!
Ooh, this is fun.
Ooh!
A little long sleeve, but then it's like backless with these sequin straps.
So cute.
Then I got this!
Look how pretty this is.
I've been loving the color purple, especially ever since I went back to brown hair.
Anything plum looks really good with my brown hair, so I've been aiming to buy more dark purple.
How does this work, guys?
It's a shawl.
I don't know where my head goes.
I think my head goes here.
So it'd go like this.
Cute little beach cover-up oh my god these are so cute little shorts also for the summer time my ass
Might be out but that's fine I'm obsessed with jeans I love jeans very me in jeans look how pretty
The wash is on me I love the like distressed look the rips and the top wash amazing thank you
So much jade in london yeah I'm gonna get ready I've been saving so many spots that I want to
Try because thank you tiktok there's so many recommendations but also for my friends I have so many places saved
So I started to make a little guide.
No, multiple guides.
Guides.
Sorry.
Like, look.
I don't know if you can tell but I have Paris brunch, coffee matcha, dinners, cafes to work.
So let's look at the coffee and matcha recommendations because I have so many saved on there.
Yesterday when I was with Eliza, she told me about this tea room that she went to and it's actually
In the area that I kind of want to venture out to today.
It's called Kiji.
Apparently, it's like obviously like the cafe section on the bottom part, but then on the top section it's like
Classic Japanese tea room where you like take off your shoes and you sit on the floor.
So I might go there because I just know that matcha would be delicious and that's so like cozy.
We'll see where my day takes me.
I actually have to film something really quickly.
Do some errands in the apartment and then we're heading out for the day.
And then I have a workout class at 6 30 I think.
Snake and Twist, insane workout.
Like you're shaking and crying and feel like you're training for like survival survival survivor
But it's great I love it it's kind of exhilarating okay off we go let's
Go
It's so
Rainy.
I'm heading to a little brunch with
A new friend.
I've been making a lot of new friends since being in Paris, and I love it.
I think it's a lot because of social media.
Like, a lot of them reach out, or I reach out, because we see we're in the same city.
So it's amazing.
It's been so fun to, like, meet new people.
But yeah, I'm going to this place called Echo.
It's really chilly today, so I had to, like, bring out a warmer coat, because it's so cold today.
And we're going to see what we end up doing for the rest of the day.
It is Valentine's Day.
So hopefully I'll see my girls later for a little Galentine's.
I think we will do something but we shall see what we're up to I'm also loving my outfit.
It's very like simple chic I wish I give you guys a fit check but I rushed out the house
This morning so I could make it on time and I Am on time.
So it's great.
Yeah, I like my outfit.
I'll show you guys later.
Let's go get some yummy food and vibe
Can you plug your brand?
Because this is insane.
This is trash.
I'm Tate.
This is trash, of course.
And like...
We're a little moment.
She's a little Valencia bitch.
Here's another little Valencia bitch.
Okay, this is amazing.
This could be your next one.
Okay, it might be.
Inspired by New York.
Yes.
So he basically...
You take a quiz, right?
Yeah.
And he personalizes your delicious, gorgeous, sexy bag for you.
She's based on childhood nostalgia, consumption.
Yes.
She's all the things we trash.
This is actually a $1 bill from the streets of the East Village.
Oh, my God.
That was my favorite thing was waking up in the morning on the weekend and seeing what trash would be
Out from the night before.
Because I looked on 9th and 2nd.
Oh, my God.
Anyway, this is a real camera.
Yes.
So that's, oh, my God.
So she is turned on.
That's so cool.
Yeah, take a photo with her Okay, wait, wait I'm gonna take a photo of you Did it do it?
I think it took it Oh my god And then There's a teeny tiny Little SD card here Stop Yeah
Hey Oh my god I'm so excited So if you have the plug for this I do I literally have
It in my bag I can like export it to my Or You could plug it in Oh my god
How cute So he literally customized This This city bag for me Based off of my childhood Like favorites Yeah
My favorite color She's a DASA bag She's a Hadassah bag This is an iPod and then wait turn it
Because I think this is my favorite part that I heart New York and a little visa His first trip
To Paris, so I'm gonna put his little out here if you guys are interested in what your own customized
Trash bag
The first time
I
Saw the
Okay, ignore how dark it is in this apartment right now, but I never showed you guys my outfit and
I really wanted to because I love it.
I just got home.
I have been wandering around literally all day, cafe hopping, walking around.
It's so like lively, busy, but this is the outfit.
It is so cold today.
I love these jeans that I got in the Jada London PR that I showed you guys.
They're the perfect amount of bagginess.
And then I'm wearing this heaven mayhem belt, my little tabbies, a black long sleeve from Skims, their coat.
I just felt really cute and diva.
And that's Thanks for watching.
I'm gonna go do some work now until later tonight.
I don't really know what the plan is.
We were gonna go to a soccer game, I'm sorry, a football game, but then we decided last minute not
To go, so we'll see what we end up doing instead.
But it's been a lovely day, and I've been loving this cafe hopping, journaling, reading, matcha, tea, whatever vibe I've
Been on, and then just walking around and exploring.
It's been really nice.
It's been a lovely day.
It's 6 p.m.
In 20 minutes.
Well, I'll see you at tryouts.
Alright, CJ.
That was amazing to watch.
She came up to you, she was very nice, warm.
Oh my god, amazing.
Say hi, Eric.
Hi, what's up?
No, you're supposed to sip it.
I am supposed to sip it.
Because it's fully champagne.
I was like, you're finally going to drink it, right?
No, I did not drink it, right?
I'm gonna take a picture right now.
Oh, you have pizza?
It's like a dessert!
Oh my god!
Put it in my glass!
Oh my god, wait!
Give me some pointers!
So you learn how to do it the right way.
Ooooooh!
I gotta do it right!
How much is it?
It's two different.
Thank
You.
Good
Morning,
Everybody.
I am getting ready to head out.
I'm still sleepy, hence why my eyes are splinting.
Also, it's really sunny out today, which is surprising because it was supposed to rain, from what I
Understand, and like a lot.
It is a Monday, which means it is a work day.
I don't have classes Mondays.
My school actually is not even open on Mondays, from what I understand, so that's kind of cool.
So I use my Mondays to go to a cafe, get any homework done, editing done, things of that nature.
So we are heading out to a cafe.
Gonna go get a lovely coffee, be productive.
I think my roommate Mariana is gonna join me.
And it should be a chill little day.
There's also a little Galentine's happening tonight with some of my friends.
I'm really really excited and I have a Pilates class.
Or I have a Legree class.
I explained Legree in one of my other videos.
It looks like reformer, but it does certain things a reformer doesn't and it's a lot more intense.
So I'm excited because I haven't worked on in a few days and I feel like I need it anyways
I'm gonna stop blabbing Let me show you guys my outfit because I really like it and a few of
You guys will recognize the jacket If you watched my last video you saw me trying on this beautiful piece
At the vintage store I really need to clean the mirror after showing you guys my outfit But it is
Perfection and I could not leave without getting it It was actually the last jacket they had in the store
Which is funny because like a vintage store is always one-of-a-kind pieces but they were actually selling a brand and
They had just received the shipment the day before and they're like within 24 hours everything sold Out and I
Got the last one I was so excited because it is like so unique and beautiful and perfect and I'm
Such a jacket Girl, I love me a good sexy chic coat.
I'm gonna stop rambling.
I really need to go.
I'm running a little bit late Anyways, let's head out
I'm
Just shifting my attention to you I'm
Heading to my workout class right now and then going
Straight from there to Galentine's and I'm really excited and it's nice too because it's in the same area as
My workout class which I so didn't plan and it's been a really productive day.
I haven't vlogged since like this morning my first round of editing because I've been doing that all day and
It's like boring like who cares but it should be a fun little evening
Oh my god, I died.
I just died.
Look who greeted me at the door.
Hi!
Say hi to the vlog!
Galentines!
Hi Santa!
Hi Plum!
You're so cute!
Desire!
The Thank
You.
Thank